Hey there, welcome to Kansas City.
Good.
Congratu- congratulations. Appreciate
you. Appreciate you. Okay, here's our
local media. You'll see these guys a lot
while you when you get here.
And they're just going to ask you some
questions and we'll let you go
celebrate.
Okay, we're going to start with Sam
McDowell with Kansas City Star.
Hey, what's up, man? I just I got a
couple things for you, but wonder first
just your reaction and maybe your
pre-draft communication with the Chiefs.
Did this come as a surprise to you?
I mean, obviously I think it's obvious
case where you know,
you know, everybody was saying you know,
the needs for my position or what not,
but to me like, you know, the the the
communication with the Chiefs wasn't
really like too much too so I didn't
really expect it I'll say.
But just really my reaction at the time
of getting picked, you know, I all my
emotions came out when I seen that
Kansas City, you know, number come
across my phone. You know, it was just a
blessing.
And then just I wonder your draft day
experience. I mean, obviously I know
you're at the draft, but who you watched
it with and and who's important to you
in that room?
Sure. Two of my brothers, two of my
sisters, you know, both my parents,
grandma, grandpa, you know, everybody.
It took a village to get where I'm at.
So
you know, everybody just enjoying this
experience with me.
Okay, let's go next to Matt Derrick with
Chiefs Digest.
Go ahead, Matt.
Hey, Mansour, congratulations and I hope
I got your name correct there. Is it
Mansour? Mansour, perfect. Excellent.
You you know,
how did you have you watched much of
Trent McDuffie? Obviously he was the guy
that you're kind of going to be
replacing at least on the roster. Did
you watch him play much and have any
thoughts about him as a player?
No, for sure he's a great player. You
know, I like to study all types of guys
in the league. You know, and he he's one
of the best to do it especially with his
versatility. So you know, just not
knowing where I'm going to fit in
I can fit in anywhere in that defense
back as defense. So really just excited
to step in and make an impact.
And I know you played obviously a lot on
the boundary and as a as an outside
corner. What's your comfort level as far
as playing inside the slot corner if
that's what the Chiefs ask you to do?
Super comfortable. You know, I love
playing inside. I think it's almost even
more fun. You know, you're closer to the
ball. You know, you're in more run fits.
You can blitz more. You know, you have
more responsibility. So I think to me
the more responsibility the funner it
is.
So I'm excited.
Let's go next to Todd Leabo.
A couple questions. First off, I know
your head's spinning. Who called you
from the Chiefs? Who did you get to talk
to? Do you and can you kind of let us
know what you heard on those
conversations?
I'mma be 100% honest. You know, when
they when they called me, I just started
crying. I don't know who was talking. I
was just saying thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
But then I talked to I remember just
talking to Coach Reed.
You know, Mr. Veach. I just remember
those two specifically once I kind of
winded down a little bit. But you know,
it was it was
it was a great moment.
And tell me about your progression. You
started with Virginia Tech, you ended
with a year at LSU.
What did you feel that move to LSU meant
for you as far as getting yourself to
this level?
No, for sure it just it gave me the
platform. You know, I just want I'm
always a guy who runs to competition.
You know, I think LSU that was one of
the hardest tasks. I took a chance.
I bet on myself and it paid off. So you
know, just playing with great guys,
surrounded myself with the best
competition.
I just love that.
We'll go next to Jesse Newell.
Hey, Mansour. I got a couple for you.
First off, you said that a lot of tears
right after you were picked. Can you
take me through the emotions? What was
going through your mind?
So you know, as I get the phone call
and you know, they traded up. So then I
was like, dang, I wanted to go to the
Chiefs, but you know, I just wasn't
expecting it. So I was like, yeah, here
it goes. Then I look down and I'm like I
look around like for a quick second.
And then I pick up the phone and then
I'm like, whoa, like this is crazy. And
then you know, that's when just the the
emotion came to me and you know, I was
just so blessed to you know, be on a
team like this.
And I think you said on TV they made the
best move in the draft to take you. Can
you explain what you meant by that?
It's the best move. You know, I truly
believe defense wins championships.
You know, let alone we know what the
offense you know,
we already have now. You know, the
defense it just makes our job even even
even easier.
So really just being able to step in and
you see
you know, the impact. You know, now that
the league is such a passing league and
you know, everybody wants to score
points. So I'm here to shut it down. So
I think that's the best move you can
make.
Let's go next to Nick Jacobs.
And City, I have a follow up if I can,
please. Mansour, for you, what is it
about football that you love?
I love I love everything about it. I
love the violence of the sport.
And again, on a different note, I love
the relationships it brings. You know,
it just bring me around so many great
people
and so many different bridges more than
after football.
You know, I just think it's a beautiful
game and I'm just glad to be a part of
it.
And for you kind of watching a Steve
Spagnuolo scheme, what is it that
excites you about being able to play in
that style? Man, I couldn't ask for
anything better. You know, just Spags,
you know, the things I hear about him
and just you know, being on a Zoom call.
I did a Zoom call with him and just the
defense that he has, just the the the
flexibility you can play with and you
can you can play ball. And I think
that's what fits me best. You know, just
the way I play ball with anticipation
and you know, and knowledge. You know, I
think it just fits me great.
We'll go next to Steve Walls. Go ahead,
Steve.
Hey, what's up, Mansour?
Congratulations, man. Appreciate you.
Hey, you talked about relationships. I
believe one of your brothers that you
played with at VT, man, Chamarri Conner.
He was a senior, you was a freshman at
VT. Just talk about being able to be on
a team, you know, again with him. For
sure. You know, when I came to Virginia
Tech, I was a freshman and Chamarri was
you know, this big old senior type of
dude. Like I really looked up to him.
Like you know, I was like, oh, that's
what a college player is like. So just
being around Chamarri and just you know,
that's one of the best players I've ever
played with and you know, we talked a
little bit before the draft that we hope
to get play with each other. But now
you know, it's just we I got some old
pictures I need to repost. But you know,
it'd be a blessing.
Has he has he called you?
No, I haven't been able to check my
phone. He texted me like he texted me
like 10 minutes before the draft though.
And he just said let me know if you need
anything. You know, he might have known
something I didn't though, apparently.
We'll go next to Vahe Gregorian. Go
ahead, Vahe.
Hey, Mansour. Congratulations.
What What are you said this a little
bit, but what did it mean to you that
they drafted up up for you? I mean, does
it come with a little extra sense of
responsibility and excitement and all
the follow up said too.
For sure. You know, I think pressure or
privilege, you know, I don't really take
it as if like you know, I got more
weight on my shoulders or anything. But
it just shows you know, the how much
they wanted me and you want to be
somewhere you're where you want to. You
can't ask for anything better than that.
So
you know, I'm just glad to be a part of
this program
organization and I'm ready to get
started.
And a little related to the question
about Chamarri. Have you gotten to know
Tyrann Mathieu at all or
is he a guy that you've
looked up to and followed and maybe
heard from?
For sure. Honey Badger has to be a top
three players you know, in all time
especially in college football.
But you know, I just I watch his podcast
a lot you know, him being me going to
LSU and you know, him
being from Louisiana. You know, I just
heard about you know, Coach Andy Reid's
practices. So I've already been prepared
for that.
And then really just
him supporting me throughout this
process and even when I committed to
LSU, you know, welcome me into the
brotherhood.
Okay, perfect. Let's
We have three more left. Go ahead, Mark.
Hey, Mansour. Welcome here to Kansas
City.
Not a lot of top 10 picks get
immediately play for a team that has
championship aspirations. I'm wondering
how excited are you to get here and play
for the Kansas City Chiefs?
That's what I was saying. I just really
think there's no better opportunity. You
know, a lot of top 10 teams like you
know, they're really not that too not
good. But that's not the
situation here. You know, we have a
championship team. Just had one little
down year. But you know, we're right
back to it. You know, with the
expectations that are here, you know,
I'm expecting to live up to them. So I'm
ready to go.
Okay, let's go next to Herbie. Go ahead,
Herbie.
Hey, Mansour. Along with everyone else,
congratulations and welcome to Kansas
City.
You mentioned at the start of this that
you always wanted to play for the
Chiefs. Why did you want to play for the
Chiefs?
You said why did I want to play for the
Chiefs? Yes. For sure.
Coach Spags,
you know, just the defense. And then on
top of that, you know, the whole
everything. The culture, you know, how
much the fan base, the way y'all love
the team.
You know, really it's a winning program.
You know, you know who's on the other
side of the ball. So then at the at the
same time, you know, the defense just
the versatility. You get to play with
they're not going to corner hold you in
one spot. You can you can be a ball
player. So I think that's the best
situation I can ask for.
Okay, last one for you and
go ahead, Darren.
Hey, thank you. Mansour, welcome to
Kansas City. We'll we'll welcome you
when you get here, man. I think you're
going to enjoy it very much. Look, you
were you were one of the best players at
your position in college football. How
do you feel like playing at a big time
program, playing in the swamp, that type
of atmosphere will will allow you to
transfer easily over here to Kansas
City?
For sure. I played at Virginia Tech,
too, and that environment is no slouch
either. So you know, every place I've
been at, you know, it's been crazy
environments. Just going to LSU, you
know, the expectations are crazy in the
SEC. You know, it's almost even crazier
in the league, I would say. So just you
know, coming to the league, you know,
really not too much of a difference for
me. You know, I thrive and I love
playing in these you know, pressure
situations and these pressure moments.
So it's a blessing.
Okay, that's all we have for you and
Chelsea will tell you what's next.